http://www.keeleyfunds.com/privacy.php

info@KeeleyFunds.com
Distributed by:
Sales Charge / Break Points & 12B-1 Fees
NAV Purchases (no load)
Sales Charge / Break Points & 12B-1 Fees
NAV Purchases (no load)
Privacy Policy
KEELEY Funds, Inc.
PRIVACY STATEMENT
Protecting your personal information is an important priority for us. Our privacy policy is designed to support this objective. We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources: Information we receive from you on applications or on other forms; correspondence or conversations, such as your name, address, social security number, assets, income and date of birth.
Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others, such as your account numbers and balances, transaction history, parties to transactions, cost basis information and other financial information. We do not disclose any nonpublic information about our current or former consumers or customers to nonaffiliated third parties, except as permitted by law. G.distributors, LLC is the Distributor and Keeley-Teton Advisors, LLC is the Investment Adviser for the KEELEY Funds, Inc.
We restrict access to your nonpublic information to those persons who require such information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.
KEELEY Funds, Inc.
111 West Jackson
Suite 810
Chicago, IL 60604
312-786-5050
800-422-3554
Fax: 312-786-5003
G.distributors, LLC, Distributor - Member FINRA
Keeley-Teton Advisors, LLC, Advisor
111 West Jackson
Suite 810
Chicago, IL 60604
312-786-5000
800-422-3554
Fax: 312-786-5002
Investors should carefully consider the investment objectives, risks, charges and expenses of the Fund before investing. The prospectus, which contains more complete information about this and other matters, should be read carefully before investing. To obtain a prospectus, please call 800-422-3554 or visit keeleyfunds.com.
